Haverhill, Mass. First Congregational Church records, 1719-2012.
Congregational Library Archives
- First Parish Church records, 1719 1756; 1719-1756; 9 Folders
  - Relations S-W, 1719 1742; 1719-1742 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Webster, Tryphena, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 28)
    - Webster, Tryphena, 1731 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 29)
    - Weed, Mary, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 30)
    - White, Abigail, 1727 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 31)
    - White, James, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 32)
    - White, Nicholas, 1719 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 33)
    - White, Timothy, 1725 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 34)
    - Whittaker, Jacobs, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 35)
    - Whittaker, Mary, 1727 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 36)
    - Whittaker, Mary, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 37)
    - Whittaker, Sarah, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 38)
    - Whittaker, William, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 39)
    - Whittier, Nathaniel, 1729 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 40)
    - Whittier, William, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 41)
    - Wilson, Rebecca, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 42)
    - Wincoll, Olive, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 43)
    - Wise, Abigail, 1742 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 44)
    - Worthen, Hannah, 1728 (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 45)
  - Disciplinary records, 1726 1738; 1726-1738 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    These church records were digitized as part of the New England's Hidden Histories project. Digital reproductions are available to view online.
    This folder contains records of disciplinary cases in Haverhill. Punishment in many cases usually consisted of censure — a temporary restriction from attending services and participating in church business — until the guilty party made a formal confession or request for forgiveness.
  - Financial records, 1732 1756; 1732-1756 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    The Deacon White financial records were digitized as part of the New England's Hidden Histories project. Digital reproductions are available to view online.
    The Rev. Edward Barnard financial pamphlet was digitized as part of the New England's Hidden Histories project. Digital reproductions are available to view online.
    The Rev. Edward Barnard financial booklet was digitized as part of the New England's Hidden Histories project. Digital reproductions are available to view online.
    This folder contains the financial records of the First Parish and one of its early ministers. A two page document attributed to Deacon White contains information on parish expenses, tax rates, and meeting minutes. A string bound pamphlet lists the accounts of Rev. Edward Barnard. Many of the entries in the ledger are paired with an entry on the following page: accounts paid with cash or in-kind. A booklet kept by Rev. Edward Barnard contains a list of presents, mostly foodstuffs, received as part of his salary, official or otherwise.
    Separated Materials
    The Edward Barnard items were removed from the John Barnard papers (MS0790) in 2013 and placed into this collection in anticipation of digitization for the New England's Hidden Histories project.
- North Congregational Church records, 1824 2001; 1824-2001; 96 Files; (29 volumes, 67 folders)
  This series contains records created by the North Congregational Church in Haverhill, Massachusetts. The materials within this series contain church meeting minutes, membership records, annual reports, Sunday school records, financial records, the records of church committees and social groups, as well as the personal papers of select ministers.
  - Church and society records, 1824 2001; 1824-2001; 37 Files; (6 volumes, 31 folders)
    This sub-series contains the administrative records of the North Congregational Church and parish society as well as membership records. Within this sub-series are church meeting minutes, letters of dismission and admission, vital records, disciplinary records, and reports.
    - The Book of Remembrance, 1824 2001; 1824-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      This disbound volume is somewhat confusing and difficult to classify; it appears to include records and materials related to both the North Congregational Church and the First Congregational Church. As the volume appears to begin with the North Congregational Church it has been placed here within the arrangement.
    - Dismissions, 1838 1897; 1838, 1894-1897 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dismissions, 1898 1903; 1898-1903 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Dismissions, 1904 1906; 1904-1906 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Dismissions, 1907 1909; 1907-1909 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Dismissions, 1910 1913; 1910-1913 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Dismissions, 1914 1916; 1914-1916, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Membership register and vital records, 1859 1933; 1859-1933 (Box 2, Volume 1)
    - Church records, 1859 1899; 1859-1899 (Box 1, Volume 2)
    - Church records, 1900 1932; 1900-1932 (Box 1, Volume 3)
    - Clerk's records, 1859 1880; 1859-1880 (Box 2, Volume 2)
    - Clerk's records, 1880 1916; 1880-1916 (Box 2, Volume 3)
    - Clerk's records, 1917 1947; 1917-1947 (Box 2, Volume 4)
    - Covenant standing rules, 1866 1875; 1866, 1875 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      The item from 1875 was removed from the Church records and orders of worship, 1934-1950 folder.
    - Excommunication of Olive Snow, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Church manual, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Directories, 1892 1914; 1892-1914 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Admissions, 1893 1896; 1893-1896 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Admissions, 1897 1900; 1897-1900 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Admissions, 1901 1903; 1901-1903 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Admissions, 1904 1911; 1904-1911 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Admissions, 1912 1914; 1912-1914 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Admissions, 1915 1916; 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Ecclesiastical council records, 1894 1902; 1894-1902 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Annual reports, 1894 1910; 1894, 1902-1910 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Clerk's reports, 1895 1910; 1895-1910 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Membership reports and vital records, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Ecclesiastical council records, 1905 1916; 1905-1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - George C. How appreciation, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      This material was removed from the Annual reports, 1894, 1902-1910 folder for preservation and descriptive reasons.
    - Annual reports, 1913 1916; 1913-1916 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Church records and by-laws, 1928 1955; 1928-1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      These materials were removed from the Church records, 1917-1947 folder for preservation and descriptive reasons.
    - Members addresses, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Church records, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      These materials were removed from the Church records, 1859-1899 folder for preservation reasons.
    - Seventy-fifth anniversary program, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      These records were originally filed with the North Parish Community Church records.
    - Church records and orders of worship, 1934 1950; 1934-1950 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Annual reports, 1936 1939; 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Members list, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - North Church Sunday School records, 1859 1923; 1859-1923; 13 Files; (11 volumes, 2 folders)
    This sub-series contains the administrative, financial, and operational records of the North Church Sunday School. Of particular note are the in-depth attendance records and reports.
    - Sunday School attendance and recapitulation records, 1859 1869; 1859-1869 (Box 4, Volume 8)
    - Sunday School treasurer's book, 1870 1916; 1870-1916 (Box 3, Volume 1)
    - Sunday School records, 1872 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    - Sunday School records, 1873 (Box 4, Volume 10)
    - Sunday School records, 1879 1884; 1879-1884 (Box 4, Volume 11)
    - Sunday School treasurer's book, 1881 1891; 1881-1891 (Box 4, Volume 12)
    - Sunday School weekly attendance and minutes, 1886 1892; 1886-1892 (Box 4, Volume 13)
    - Sunday School classes and student lists, 1891 (Box 4, Volume 14)
    - Sunday School records, 1892 1898; 1892-1898 (Box 4, Volume 15)
    - Sunday School records, 1898 1908; 1898-1908 (Box 4, Volume 16)
    - Sunday School reports, 1895 1899; 1895-1899 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Sunday School financial reports, 1900 1910; 1900-1910 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - John Ward School records, 1906 1923; 1906-1923 (Box 5, Volume 1)
  - Financial and building records, 1859 1943; 1859-1943; 21 Files; (9 volumes, 12 folders)
    This sub-series contains the financial records of the North Congregational Church as well as records related to the maintenance and operation of the church building. Included in the sub-series are pew deeds and pew plans, account books, pledge books, and treasurer reports.
    - Assessment book, 1859 1861; 1859-1861 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    - Building fund donations, 1859 1861; 1859-1861 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Statements of construction cost, 1859 1862; 1859, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Pew deeds and records, 1859 1864; 1859-1864 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Pew plan and owner chart, 1860 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Pew deeds and records, 1869 1925; 1869-1925 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Parsonage financial and legal records, 1889 1924; 1889-1924 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1895 1910; 1895-1899, 1910 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer's book, 1904 1928; 1904-1928 (Box 4, Volume 1)
    - Account book, 1904 1931; 1904-1931 (Box 2, Volume 6)
    - Trust fund records and will extracts, 1904 1937; 1904-1937 (Box 2, Volume 7)
    - Statement of accounts, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      This record was originally filed with the North Parish Community Church records.
    - Pew account book, 1913 1922; 1913-1922 (Box 1, Volume 4)
    - Cash book, 1914 1919; 1914-1919 (Box 4, Volume 2)
    - Building financial records, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Building financial records, 1917 1918; 1917-1918, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Cash book, 1926 1929; 1926-1929 (Box 10, Volume 1)
    - Call for donations, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Tentative budgets, 1942 1943; 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Pledge book, undated (Box 4, Volume 3)
    - Pledge book, undated (Box 4, Volume 4)
  - Church groups and committees, 1874 1926; 1874-1926; 21 Files; (3 volumes, 18 folders)
    This sub-series contains the records of social groups and committees at the North Congregational Church.
    - Church Committee records, 1874 1917; 1874-1917 (Box 4, Volume 5)
    - Prudential Committee correspondence, 1880 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Industrial Society records, 1888 1896; 1888-1896 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Industrial Society records, 1888 1899; 1888-1899 (Box 4, Volume 6)
    - Young People's Christian Association records, 1890 1904; 1890-1904 (Box 4, Volume 7)
    - Industrial Society reports, 1893 1898; 1893-1898 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Reading Room reports, 1894 1895; 1894-1895 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bethany Association reports, 1894 1898; 1894-1898 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Pentucket Mission Band reports, 1894 1899; 1894-1899 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Woman's Missionary Society reports, 1894 1901; 1894-1901 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Concord Club report, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Librarian's report, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Birthday Offering Society reports, 1895 1899; 1895, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1895 1911; 1895-1911 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Standing Committee records, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Chinese Mission Sunday School reports, 1896 1901; 1896-1901 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Visitation appointee list, 1897 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Men's League constitution and records, 1898, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - North Church Guild reports, 1899 1901; 1899-1901 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Committee of Sickness report, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Boy Scouts Troop 2 records, 1911 1926; 1911-1926 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ministerial papers, 1894 1911; 1894-1911; 4 Folders
    This sub-series contains the personal papers and reports of a select few ministers from the North Congregational Church.
    - Rev. George H. Reed papers, 1894 1898; 1894-1898 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Arthur S. Burrill report, 1896 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Rev. James S. Williamson papers, 1899 1910; 1899-1910 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Rev. J. Derbyshire papers, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Centre Congregational Church records, 1859 1942; 1859-1942; 12 Files; (1 volume, 11 folders)
  This series contains the records of the Centre Congregational Church in Haverhill, Massachusetts. This series includes administrative records, financial records, membership records, and the records of the Ladies Society.
  - Requests for dismission, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - List of church members, 1862 1917; 1862-1917 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Parish list, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sevent-fifth anniversary exercises, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annual reports, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Membership records and annual reports, 1912 1913; 1912-1913 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Membership records and annual reports, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual reports, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Membership records and reports, 1916 1917; 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Financial records, 1916 1924; circa 1916-1924 (Box 1, Volume 1)
  - Annual reports, 1918 1919; 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ladies' Society membership, 1926 1942; 1926-1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- First Congregational Church records, 1900 2011; 1900-2011; 197 Files; (14 volumes, 172 folders, 9 tapes)
  This series contains the records of the First Congregational Church in Haverhill, Massachusetts. This series contains administrative records, the records of social groups and committees, newsletters and orders of service, financial records, building records, architectural drawings, video records, photographs, and sermon manuscripts.
  - Image and audiovisual materials, 1900 2001; 1900-2001; 22 Files; (13 folders, 9 tapes)
    This sub-series contains all visual and audiovisual materials related to the First Congregational Church. The majority of these materials are related to everyday church life and special events.
    - Photographs of Dr. H.J. Whitney and Lourie Ann Whitney in Fuzhou, China, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Postcards, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Choir slides, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Church suppers slides, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Theater production slides, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Church fairs and festivities slides, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Easter slides, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Church life slides, circa 1955 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      This folder of slides also contains an index of the slides which identify what is captured in many of them.
    - Men's Club and building campaign slides, circa 1955 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - 150th state conference slides, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Christmas bazaar slides, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Christmas pageant, 1987 (Box 10, Tape 1)
    - Women's Guild auction, 1988 (Box 10, Tape 2)
    - Holiday festivities, 1988 1989; 1988-1989 (Box 10, Tape 3)
    - Guild auction and Christmas musical, 1989 (Box 10, Tape 4)
    - Building and construction photographs, 1990 1999; circa 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Church life photographs, 1990 1999; circa 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Some photographs within this folder have descriptions written on the back of the photograph in pen or pencil.
    - 135th anniversary celebration, 1994 (Box 10, Tape 5)
    - 135th anniversary celebration, 1994 (Box 10, Tape 6)
    - Christmas pageant, 1996 (Box 10, Tape 7)
    - Children's pageant, 1998 (Box 10, Tape 8)
    - Winter pageant, 2001 (Box 10, Tape 9)
  - Church committees, societies, and groups, 1922 2010; 1922-2010; 45 Files; (6 volumes, 39 folders)
    This sub-series contains the records of the various social groups, philanthropic organizations, and lay committees of the First Congregational Church. Of particular note are the thorough records kept by the Women's Guild and the Diaconate. This sub-series also contains records related to youth groups, outreach efforts, and planning for the church's future.
    - Thoughtful Circle financial records, 1922 1951; 1922-1951 (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Women's Guild financial records, 1944 1946; 1944-1946 (Box 3, Volume 2)
    - Women's Guild financial records, 1946 1950; 1946-1950 (Box 9, Volume 1)
    - Women's Guild financial records, 1950 1954; 1950-1954 (Box 9, Volume 2)
    - Women's Guild financial records, 1951 1979; 1951-1979 (Box 9, Volume 3)
    - Women's Guild annual reports, 1950 1952; 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Women's Guild annual reports, 1953 1961; 1953-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Women's Guild annual reports, 1962 1967; 1962-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Women's Guild annual reports, 1992 2004; 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Women's Guild minutes, 1957 1960; 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Women's Guild minutes, 1961 1963; 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Women's Guild records, 1967 1968; 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Women's Guild records, 1969 1975; 1969-1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Women's Guild records, 1976 1982; 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Women's Guild records, 1983 1985; 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Women's Guild records, 1988 1995; 1988-1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Women's Guild records, 1995 1998; 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Women's Guild records, 1999 2004; 1999-2004 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Women's Guild records, 1997 2009; 1997-2009 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      This folder appears to contain records which were forwarded to the Women's Guild and includes a letter of complaint, some financial records, a letter of introduction, and records relating to a posthumous donation.
    - Women's Guild directories, 1969 2002; 1969-2002, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Women's Guild by-laws, 1973 1991; 1973, 1988, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Women's Guild rededication scrapbook, 1984 (Box 9, Volume 4)
    - Women's Guild membership list, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Women's Guild bicentennial quilt, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Women's Guild sponsorships through World Vision, 1994 2010; 1994-2010 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Women's Guild mission statement, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Women's Guild history and clippings, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - The Players programs, 1946 1952; 1946-1952 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Dedication committee, 1951 1968; 1951-1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Board of deacons and deaconesses records, 1954 1970; 1954-1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Diaconate records, 1971 1973; 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Diaconate records, 1974 1986; 1974-1986 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Diaconate records, 1987 1991; 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Diaconate records, 1992 1995; 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Diaconate records, 1996 2003; 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Olive Maynard Society history and clippings, 1964 1983; 1964-1983 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Christian Outreach Committee records, 1971 1979; 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Christian Outreach Committee records, 1980 1981; 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      This folder contains records related to an effort by Rev. Ephron Hernandez to gather a Hispanic Congregation and use the First Church facilities as a base for his ministry.
    - Long Range Planning Committee records, 1971 1975; 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Long Range Planning Committee records, 1980 1991; 1980-1991 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      This folder contains a major self-appraisal study and a "Parish Profile Inventory" created by the Center for Social and Religious Research at the Hartford Seminary.
    - Religious Education Committee records, 1974 1981; 1974-1981 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Youth program participants, 1978 1979; 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Youth fellowship program records, 1981, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Sunday school registrations, 1989 1991; 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Girl Scout sponsorships, 1998 1999; 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Church and membership records, 1939 2011; 1939-2011; 72 Files; (6 volumes, 64 folders)
    This sub-series contains the administrative records of the First Congregational Church and records related to the membership of the church. Included in this sub-series are annual reports, letters of admission and dismission, correspondence, council records, vital records, policy documents, anniversary records, registers, and survey results.
    - Church histories and clippings, 1930 2006; 1930-2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Church by-laws, 1939 2010; 1939-2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bequest and furniture inventory cards, 1939 1969; 1939-1969 (Box 11)
      It is very likely that these cards were created at the time of the merger between the North and First churches. Another possibility is that cards from both churches were combined.
    - Baptismal records, 1939 1972; 1939-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Attendance records, 1945 1972; 1945-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Annual reports, 1947 1952; 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Annual reports, 1952 1959; 1952-1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Annual reports, 1960 1965; 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Annual reports, 1966 1970; 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Annual reports, 1971 1975; 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Annual reports, 1976 1980; 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Annual reports, 1981 1985; 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Annual reports, 1986 1990; 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Annual reports, 1991 1995; 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Annual reports, 1996 2000; 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Annual reports, 2001 2005; 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Annual reports, 2006 2011; 2006-2011 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Church register and records, 1951 1960; 1951-1960 (Box 7, Volume 1)
    - Church register and records, 1951 1979; 1951-1979 (Box 7, Volume 2)
    - Letters of dismission, 1951 1962; 1951-1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Letters of dismission, 1962 1974; 1962-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Membership transfers, 1953 1961; 1953-1961 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Membership transfers, 1962 1975; 1962-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Communications and Correspondence, 1953 1958; 1953-1958 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Communications and Correspondence, 1959 1966; 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Communications and Correspondence, 1967 1974; 1967-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Communications and Correspondence, 1975 1976; 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Communications and Correspondence, 1976 1985; 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Communications and Correspondence, 1993 1999; 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Centennial celebration, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Church Council records, 1960 1971; 1960-1971 (Box 7, Volume 5)
    - Church Council records, 1971 1980; 1971-1980 (Box 7, Volume 6)
    - Church Council records, 1980 1983; 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Church Council records, 1984 1986; 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Church Council records, 1987 1988; 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Church Council records, 1989 1990; 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Church Council records, 1991 1992; 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Church Council records, 1993 1996; 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Church Council records, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Church Council records, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Church Council records, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Church Council records, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
    - Church Council records, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
    - Church Council records, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
    - Church Council records, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Church Council records, 2004 2006; 2004-2006 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Church Council records, 2007 2011; 2007-2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - 110th anniversary celebration, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Richard Stearns moderator records, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Membership lists, 1972 1999; 1972-1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Necrology, 1973 1978; 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Necrology, 1985 1989; 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Necrology, 1990 1997; 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)